Cunard Lines
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Cunard Lines
2.1.1.1.5
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1177
- Cunard Lines, 2.1.1.1.5
  - Parlor, copy, before 1916; 28; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Picture over fireplace, before 1916; 29; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - The Aquitania out of water, before 1916; 30; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - People looking at the propeller of the Aquitinia, before 1916; 31; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Painting over a table, before 1916; 32; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Painting over a table, before 1916; 33; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Looking at propeller of the Aquitania, before 1916; 34; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Subway train in smokestack of the Aquitania, before 1916; 35; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - The Aquitania out of water, before 1916; 36; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Hallway of the Aquitania, before 1916; 37; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - View of empty deck, before 1916; 38; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Small boats next to large ship, before 1916; 39; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - View of Aquitania's propellers, before 1916; 40; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Table and chairs, before 1916; 41; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Bedroom, before 1916; 42; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Ship deck, before 1916; 43; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Table and foreplace in stateroom, before 1916; 44; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Swimming pool? on ship, before 1916; 45; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Lounge, before 1916; 46; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Small boat on the Aquitania, before 1916; 47; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Tables and chairs on deck, before 1916; 48; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Dining room on the Aquitania, before 1916; 49; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Dining room, before 1916; 50; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Buildings and smokwstacks, before 1916; 51; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Ship gymnasium, before 1916; 52; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  Box 1178
- Cunard Lines, 2.1.1.1.5
  - Lounge, before 1916; 1; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Lounge, before 1916; 2; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Top of staircase, before 1916; 3; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Lifeboats on the Aquitania, before 1916; 4; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Lounge, before 1916; 5; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Chairs and tables on ship, before 1916; 6; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Sitting room, before 1916; 7; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Dining room, before 1916; 8; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Sitting room, before 1916; 9; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Lounge with piano, before 1916; 10; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Cunard highway, copy, before 1916; 11; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Following the flag, copy, before 1916; 12; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Mr. Jones, before 1916; 13; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Mr. Hoblyn, before 1916; 14; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Purser of the Campania, before 1916; 15; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Captain at the Cunard Line, before 1916; 16; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Crowds at the Cunard Lines, before 1916; 17; 4x5 film (Box 1178)
  - Cunard Line, before 1916; 18; 4x5 film (Box 1178)